http://www.myparentime.com/legal/privacy.shtml

'I Know Safety' Book for Kids | Family Magazines | Amazon Gift Cards | Child Safety eBook
Please read if you have ever received an unsolicited attachment claiming to be from MyParenTime.com.
MyParenTime.com's
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
MyParenTime.com/StopSexOffenders.com/PrintableChecklists.com/JupiterParents.com (Internet websites that make up My ParenTime's Family Community), supports privacy on the Internet.
Although we do gather information about our visitors for tracking purposes (site statistics: keywords searched, amount of visits, referring websites, etc.), we do not receive any personal information via our statistical tracker.
Cookies:
MyParenTime.com/StopSexOffenders.com/PrintableChecklists.com/JupiterParents.com uses no cookies itself, although as of the year 2000 we have added occasional pop-up ads with special offers on our websites, which do contain cookies. We do not receive any information at all from this cookie.
Some websites do use cookies, which are small identifiers placed on your hard drive by that webpage's server to tell it that you've previously visited with that website.
Cookies can make things easier for you, for ie: if you order frequently from an ecommerce website - they'll be able to find your information easily when you return, which will make your checkout time shorter.
You can control and choose whether to accept cookies or not.
My ParenTime's Family Community has out-sourced most top banner ads to an advertising company which does use cookies. Please read the following information (updated 12/09) about Burstmedia, which will explain their purpose and extent of their use of cookies in their ad banners:
Updated 12/09: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
My ParenTime also includes Google ads throughout our website, which has the following policies:
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google's use of the Doubleclick DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
You may opt out of the use of the Doubleclick DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
You can opt out of any behavioral advertising served by other websites by visiting this page.
Our Visitor's Privacy:
We accept emails from children, but no personal information is asked for, and no information is shown, shared, or sold to any third party. Parents, we want to help keep your children safe and also protect their privacy as well. Please discuss with your children the use of their personal information on the Internet.
See our Internet Safety Guide for some great safety tips!
No personal information is required to join our update list. Email addresses that you provide to us for contests or visitor comments are never sold or shown to any third party.
From January-February, 2004: Please visit this page for more information. Our experience has ended - see below for helpful information. The MyParenTime.com domain name is being used without permission to send unsolicited bulk emails containing non-family-friendly information and a non-family-friendly website link. Please know that we do not condone this, and are doing everything possible to end this situation. Please do not email us asking us to remove your email address. Since no one at myparentime.com is sending any emails, we cannot help you. Unfortunately, the work is being done by spammers who are misusing the myparentime.com domain name. I am aware of the spammers and the emails they are sending. I have tried contacting their ISPs, and will continue to do so each time I discover a new IP. I have been forwarding as many spam emails as I possibly can, but I simply do not have the time to send them all. I would appreciate it if you could please locate the IP # in the full header of the email, then visit this website to discover the ISP that the spammer is using. After you discover the ISP, forward the spam email (including full headers) to their abuse department. This will help all of us caught in the loop.
2005 Update: We are finally recovering from this issue. Thanks to everyone for your support and patience during this experience.
Below you will find a few tips on responding to spam emails, which are included in the autoresponder we send when someone sends an email to a non-existing email address at myparentime.com:
Please do not reply to this message -- no one will receive it.
Due to an overwhelming amount of spam, this email address was created as a "catch-all" for all email sent to the following website contacts:
MyParenTime.com, PrintableChecklists.com, StopSexOffenders.com, and JupiterParents.com
MyParenTime.com does NOT send unsolicited emails -- we have a strict opt-in mailing list only, that sends email to our members once per month. We especially do not send anything NON-Family-Friendly.
If you are receiving spam, we offer the following tips to keep in mind:
NEVER REPLY TO SPAM EMAILS!
1. You don't want these people to know you have an active email address,
2. You may be replying to an innocent party, in which case that innocent party may receive 1000 times more emails due to the original spam emails sent (this is what was happening in my case),
3.Check the original email headers for IP address, to discover the true identity of the person sending spam. It is very easy to create a reply-to address in an email, which spammers often do.
If you are truly trying to reach someone at MyParenTime.com, PrintableChecklists.com, StopSexOffenders.com or JupiterParents.com, please visit the appropriate website for contact information.  Do not hit "reply" - no one will receive your message.
Thank you, and we apologize for the inconvenience.
My ParenTime's Family Community of Websites~
We are committed to protecting your privacy...we expect the same from our own online experiences.
If you have any questions, please feel free to Email us!
I Know Safety | MyParenTime.com Text Sponsors |
| My ParenTime Home | Printable Checklists Home | Privacy | Legal | Disclaimer | Copyright |
| About Us | Site Map | Articles | Child Safety | OPK FAQ | BBT Charting | Breastfeeding Guide |
| Hints & Tips | Online Games | Calculators | Special Reviews | Informative Websites |
| Greeting Cards | Shop | Link to Us | Reminder Service | Movie Reviews |
| Search | Our Awards | Twitter | Blog | Advertise | Text Sponsors | Hall of Shame |
| No SPAM! |
Copyright © 1997-2017, My ParenTime
No reprints without written permission.
Our Website Community is Proudly hosted by FutureQuest
Other Websites in the My ParenTime Family Community:
| stopsexoffenders.com | jupiterparents.com | printablechecklists.com | funinternetgames.com |
